Van Arsdale, Harry Oral History Project 5835 OHM
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Harry Van Arsdale Oral History Project
1988-1990
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Van Arsdale, Harry
Goodrich, Jerry
Schmidt, Hans
5835 OHM
2.89 cubic feet
1 file folder.
Interviews.
Interviews from Syracuse, Auburn, and Ithaca, New York.
5713655
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /4054: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4117 P: ILR School Photographs /4199: Kheel Center Harry Van Arsdale Labor History Project Files /4230: Maurice Neufeld Additional Files /4280 P: ILR School Ives Hallway Portrait Gallery Photographs 5206: Local 1199 Records 5206-S: Local 1199 Executive Secretary Moe Foner Records 5619: ACWA Records 5680 OH: Local 1199 Oral History Project 5685: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5745 P: ACWA Publicity Department Photographs 5780 AV: ILGWU Audio-Visual (AV) 5780 P: ILGWU Photographs 5780/002: ILGWU David Dubinsky Correspondence 5780/047: ILGWU Joint Board Dress & Waistmakers' Union of Greater New York Managers' Correspondence 5780/102 P: ILGWU Justice Photographs 5780/176 P: ILGWU Communications Department Photographs 5780/177: ILGWU Communications Department Biography Files 5850: International Brotherhood of Painters & Allied Trades, Local 677, Glaziers & Glass Workers Minutes 5852: Allied Building Trades Council of Rochester, NY, Minutes 5853: Rochester (NY) Federation of Classroom Teachers Records 5933 P: Local 1199 Photograph Files 5981 P: ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 6021 P: Theodore W. Kheel Photographs 6046: Archives Union File (AUF) 6174/001: NYSUT President's Office Files 6199/005 P: HERE Communications Department Photographs 6371 AV: Harry Kelber Audio-Visual Materials
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 28, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Goodrich, Jerry; Van Arsdale, Harry, 1905-1986.; Schmidt, Hans
5713655
- John Dombroski (b.9/22/1924) Oral History Interview, 9/7/1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  tape #1
- John Dombroski (b.9/22/1924) Oral History Interview, 9/7/1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  tape #2
- John Dombroski (b.9/22/1924) Oral History Interview, 9/7/1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  tape #3
- John Dombroski (b.9/22/1924) Oral History Interview, 9/7/1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  tape #4
- Frank Muzzy - 6/18/1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Frank Muzzy - 6/18/1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Interview w/James DeBella Rome, NY - 1/19/1989 - Restrictions Apply (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Interview w/James DeBella Rome, NY - 1/19/1989 - Restrictions Apply (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Interview w/James DeBella Rome, NY - 1/19/1989 - Restrictions Apply (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Interview w/James DeBella Rome, NY - 1/19/1989 - Restrictions Apply (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Farrell, Edward J. - Oral History Interview - 6/27/1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- William J. McLane - Oral History - 1/19/1990 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Rice, Kenneth Oral History - 1/5/1990 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Richard Clark & Chris Jacobsen - Oral History Interview - 12/8/1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Richard Clark & Chris Jacobsen - Oral History Interview - 12/8/1988 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- IBEW 181 - Utica, NY - Restrictions Apply (Box 16, Folder 1)
- IBEW 181 - Utica, NY - Restrictions Apply (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Teamsters 182 - Pres. Victor Olivadoti - Interview 4/7/1989 [Restricted] (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Teamsters 182 - Pres. Victor Olivadoti Interview 4/7/1989 [Restricted] (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Thomas J. Stern. Pres. Pressman's Union Local 58, Utica, NY 2/7/1989 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  tape 1 of 2
- Thomas J. Stern. Pres. Pressman's Union Local 58, Utica, NY 2/7/1989 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  tape 2 of 2
- Interview William Sullivan, Pres. CWA 1126, Utica, NY - 3/9/1989 - Restrictions Apply (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Interview William Sullivan, Pres. CWA 1126, Utica, NY - 3/9/1989 - Restrictions Apply (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Elmer Walter Sr. Oral History Interview - 8/16/1990 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- George Mamo Oral History Interview - 8/16/1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Harry J. Eggleston Oral History Interview, 8/16/1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)